

EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL DESIGNER

Kate Spade, NYC, March 2022-Present

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Designing site homepages, LPs, hero banners, MP4 animations and site assets for Kate Spade NY and Kate Spade Outlet using Figma, Adobe Photoshop & illustrator and After Effects.
- Working on site concept design and presenting ideation to other teams and leadership.
- Implementing ADA and WCAG standards across all site experiences.
- Communicating concise technical information to the web development, leadership and marketing teams regarding components, CSS and HTML, asset formats and delivery.
- Designing email layouts, assets and gif animations using Adobe Photoshop.
- Designing paid social media animated and static assets for Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Affiliate, Logozone and Google Performance graphics and animations using Figma and Adobe Photoshop.
- Excellent attention to detail and consistant file management and documentation of assets for reference and usage for wider team and org.

DIGITAL DESIGNER

90 Degree by Reflex, NYC, Oct 2021-March 2022

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Designing digital marketing graphics and assets using Adobe Creative Suite across four online platforms-90 Degree by Reflex, Yogalicious (using Shopify CMS) and Amazon storefronts for both brands.
- Designing digital assets and email layouts for Mailchimp email campaigns and promotions.
 Assisting the Creative Director during Photoshoots for product and lifestyle imagery.
- Maintaining and updating swatch palette library for new products and photo editing lifestyle and product imagery.

FOUNDER & DESIGNER

Alicia Seal LLC California, USA, 2015-2020

SENIOR PRINT DESIGNER

Fam Brands, California, USA, 2019-2020

PRINT DESIGNER

Hoffman Fabrics, California, USA, 2018-2019

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Elegant Clutter, Warwick, UK, 2013-2015

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Horizon RMS, Ely, UK, 2011-2013

TEXTILE DESIGNER

LI & FUNG, Hong Kong, 2006-2008

TEXTILE DESIGNER

Circle Line Design, London, UK, 2004-2006

ABOUT ME

I'm a digital designer with over fifteen years experience working within the fashion, marketing, interiors and POS design creative industries. I'm proficient with Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, Sketch, After Effects, creating prototypes in Figma, HTML and CSS. I also have extensive experience with JS, React, Redux, Reactstrap and Bootstrap for web development. I have an indepth understanding and working utilisation of e-commerce platforms Mailchimp, Shopify and Amazon Storefronts. When working on a project I am completely dedicated and enthusiastic! I'm a great communicator and I enjoy working in a team environment.

EDUCATION

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

2020 NuCamp Bootcamp California, USA

BA HONS TEXTILE DESIGN

2000–2004 Chelsea College of Art & Design, University of the Arts, London, UK

SKILL SET

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, After Effects, prototypes, Sketch, Illustration, concepting Mailchimp, Shopify, Amazon Store Fronts, HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, React, Bootstrap, Reactstrap, Github.

INTERESTS

I'm passionate about art, design and development. I enjoy creating self motivated web design and development projects and graphics in my spare time. I also love going to galleries, museums and installations to keep up to date and inspired by the latest art and culture. I enjoy walking my dog, playing video games, cycling and learning and speaking other languages such as French and Japanese.

CONTACT ME

WEB: www.aliciamorley.com **EMAIL:** alicia@aliciamorley.com

TEL: +949 522 2509

LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/alicia-morley-3ba99532

thanks!